# DANIEL **WARREN**

FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

### QUALIFICATIONS

CLEAR & SCALABLE DOCUMENTATION

OBJECT ORIENTED PROGRAMMING

COMPUTER SCIENCE FUNDAMENTALS

TRANSNATIONAL COMMUNICATIONS

DATA ANALYSIS & TROUBLESHOOTING

STRONG VERBAL & WRITTEN COMMUNICATION

PROJECT MANAGEMENT

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

C++ / C#

PYTHON

HTML/CSS/BOOTSTRAP

JAVASCRIPT

GIT/VERSION CONTROL

SQL & DATABASE MANAGEMENT

.NET FRAMEWORK

API INTEGRATION

VSCODE & OTHER IDE'S

DANIEL WARREN

DNLWRN@OUTLOOK.COM

646.907.3088

WWW.DNLWRN.COM

#### SUMMARY -

Skilled software developer with experience using professional techniques, skill, and modern development tools. Driven to high standards with a forward and computational approach to identify, formulate, and solve development problems. Ability to design a system to meet desired needs within realistic contraints while taking into account both the internal and external impact of development solutions.

#### **EXPERIENCE** -

MOOD BOUTIQUE LLC. | 2017 - 2019 DIGITAL MARKETING SPECIALIST

- •Developed marketing content for both digital and print consumption
- Provided digital marketing solutions to small businesses
- •Curated data analysis of social media platforms and website analytics
- Provided weekly updates on marketing champaigns to clients discussing stratigic initiatives and methods for improvement
- •Designed and implimented an ecommerce web-application
- Used SEO and Web Analytics to target ad champaigns toward specified audiences
- ·Produced materials accurately representing a brand and vision

BEMOBILE INC. | 2019 - 2021 SALES REPRESENTATIVE

- Developed professional client relationships to understand the needs of each client respectively
- Encouraged teamwork to meet deadlines and company goals
- Managed projects simultainiously to ensure completion of tasks in a timely fashion
- •Conducted job duties with professionalism and utilized deescalation tactics to communicate effectively with partners and clients
- · Ensured continuous training on new and upcoming technologies

FREELANCE | 2018 - 2021 SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Constructed modern web applications to meet client needs and allow for future customization of content
- Studied brands in depth to ensure longevity of application and to provide a consistent tone for client audiences
- •Integrated API's and other tools necessary for administrative tasks
- •Operated on strict deadlines and provided consistent progress updates to clients in both a written and verbal format.
- Researched new technologies to utilize in projects and expand on development skills and experience

## **EDUCATION** —

UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN-STOUT | 2017 - 2020 COMPUTER AND ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING

- •Studied hardware and software systems development
- Applied skills in prototyping and testing of hardware and software applications
- •Explored the fundamentals of computer science and the application of foundational skills in industry

THE TECH ACADEMY | 2021 - 2021 SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

- Developed technical and professional skills aligning with the needs of industry
- Gained professional experience developing in a team environment
- Aquired training with in-demand programming languages
- Researched and applied computer science fundamentals within various projects
- Utilized best practices for database management, version contol, and documentation